Now you are probably
itching to get into
the deep stuff, the
secret stuff that's going
to grow your channel.
But here is the
truth. If you were
handed a black belt
just for watching a
few training videos, you
would stick out into
the ring and you
would get a serious
ass whooping. Because you're
just not ready to
fight other black belts
yet. And black belts
are not earned for
just watching stuff. They're
earned through consistent practice
and mastering the basics
until things become second
nature. So that's all
phase two is about.
Doing your first reps
that are going to
help me transform you
from where you are
now to the Hulk
that you want to
be. So in this
phase, I'm just going
to get you to
practice the foundational YouTube
skills. Everything else is
going to be built
on top of by
creating a very simple
demo video that uses
the core elements of
effective YouTube content. Positioning,
packaging, writing and planning,
filming, editing and publishing,
as well as learning
a lesson. On top
of that, there is
practicing the art of
not giving a hoot
about a video's performance.
Because guess what? Peeps,
this video I'm about
to make you produce
is not going to
perform very well for
you. But just be
OK with that, OK?
Because the goal right
now is to just
practice the basics of
the system once. To
learn by doing, not
overthinking. To get used
to creating and removing
any emotional attachment you
have to performance. And
to help you fail
as fast as you
can. And even if
you're sitting there like,
well, I've got two
million subscribers. I think
I can skip this
bit. Don't. This isn't
beginner work. It's foundational
work. And elite pros
always focus on mastering
the foundation. And they're
not going to give
a shit about the
other people's expectations. They're
going to focus on
making sure you get
the best results. And
then they do them
better than anyone else.
Before they do the
things that only make
1 % of the
difference. So allow yourself
3 to 5 hours
to do this following
work. And that doesn't
include the time it
takes you to watch
this content. Also, if
you don't have a
teleprompter yet, you're going
to need one very
soon. The teleprompter lesson
in this phase is
going to show you
exactly what to get
and how to use
it. But it might
be worth buying that
now. So you can
get it delivered ASAP
and start working on
it.
planning and writing your
first video together.